In the last lesson we talked about how to describe data how to describe graphs.
In this lesson we're going to focus on debates.
Debate is when two sides disagree on something and they need to argue their side or make a case.
We're going to work on some useful phrases we're going to talk about the purpose of a debate we're going
to talk about how we can make a point.
Use analogies and also concede a point and then we're going to look at a real example.
Two sides of a debate issue.
So I hope you've enjoyed the course up to this point.
This will be our last full lesson.
Hope you've noticed that my hair has gotten longer throughout the course and I wonder if you've asked
yourself.
I wonder how many times he's had to wash this shirt and this shirt during the course.
The answer is probably about 15.
I've been shooting this course over the last couple months in fact and I've tried to make my appearance
about the same throughout the course to make it consistent.
So I hope you've enjoyed the course.
I hope you've got a lot out of it to this point and I hope that once we're finished with this course
you can go out there and actually use all of the stuff that you've learned.
Anyway let's get started with our last full lesson on how to debate.