I often use this expression this phrasing when I want to disagree with someone because it's really cool.
It's very powerful.
It's very interesting I'll show you how it works.
But basically what we say is if that were true why and then give an opposite example.
Now let me explain what that means.
If that were true means it is not true or at least I believe it is not true.
So you have made a statement saying that something is true.
You have said the drinking age at 21 in the USA is a good way to prevent drinking problems later in
life.
I believe that's the opposite.
If what you said were true it's not.
If it were Amber were is when we want to talk about something that's not real something that's hypothetical
and what I can do here is give an opposite example or say something that is not true that should be
true.
If you were correct which you're not Yes I could say if that were true then why isn't the rate of alcoholism
decreasing it's not decreasing right.
Why isn't it decreasing.
If that were true the rate of alcoholism should be decreasing.
You can make a statement like that if that were true then would just leave y to the side for a second.
Right.
But it isn't.
It's not see how this graph here.
It's not it's the same.
So it's a great way to show how what you're saying is illogical or there's something wrong with your
facts or whatever.
Now we can also then state we can also then state something that is true that shouldn't be there.
If you were correct.
OK.
Which means you're not correct.
So now I'm going to bring back why I really like this one especially why because it makes the other
side have to explain something.
And anytime you use the word y the other side has to explain.
And if they explain something or try to explain something that isn't right then it's it's hard to do
and maybe they're going to make themselves look very silly.
So if that were true if that were true why are there.
This is true.
Now this part is true.
Why are there so many under age drinking hyphen related deaths now.
Or I could say with the drinking age as it is I say with the drinking age as it is with the drinking
age as it is or now.
OK now you have to answer this question.
The fact is that many underage people underage means under the age of 21.
Many die.
Maybe car accidents make driving under the influence we say or drinking too much.
Whatever the reason there are lots of different possibilities.
It's very sad it's very unfortunate but I'm pointing this out to say I think you're I think you're incorrect.
If that were true why oh why did I write why.
Twice OK you get the idea.
Why are there so many underage drinking deaths now.
Question mark.
Mm hmm.
Good question.
You might have a difficult time answering that if you are the other side.
Right.
OK so this is another very powerful way.
After you say why you say something that is true that contradicts or is opposite to what would be true
if the other side was correct which they are not or you say something that should be true.
If they were correct but that is not currently true.
OK so there are two ways to do it but this beginning phrasing here.
If that were true is quite useful and quite powerful not only in debates but anytime you really want
to disagree with somebody and show the other side very simply and effectively why they're probably incorrect.
Very powerful.