In the last lesson we worked on some of the things that we can do some of the exercises we can do to
practice to improve our ability to think in English and to improve our speaking and writing habits.
In this lesson we're going to be focused on time words that means words that we can use that are related
to time that we need to use when we talk about time things in the past.
Things in the future.
Now I know that you're familiar with a lot of these words like in an ago and after later prepositions
like apt and by and around phrases like maybe back then.
But I want to make sure we go over them in this course so that to you there crystal clear that means
you completely understand them.
You know the differences between them.
You know exactly how to use them.
If you completely understand all of these and you know exactly how to use them OK perhaps you can skip
over this lesson.
I would recommend going through it because we're going to cover lots of examples lots and lots of great
examples for how to tell the difference how to know the difference between these words and phrases very
importantly how to use them.