In the last lesson we talked about how to compare things which is very important if you want to describe
the difference between that and that.
Maybe you're making a recommendation or maybe you're talking about a past experience.
In this lesson we're going to talk about inquiry how to make an inquiry or sometimes it's pronounced
inquiry basically inquiry.
An inquiry means asking someone who knows something a question so that you can get information about
what they know.
That's what it means when we do that.
We say we are inquiring so we're making an inquiry or an inquiry or we are inquiring.
We can sometimes say I would like to inquire about.
OK so in this lesson we're going to be talking about a couple of key words and phrases at the start.
Then we're going to go into a real life situation.
We're going to talk about an apartment situation if you want to rent an apartment.
You may need to call the landlord to get information about the apartment.
So we're going to do that situation so that we can go over how to use some of these words and phrases
and then we'll look at a couple of different ways to say you're welcome in English as well as talk a
little bit about how to bargain.
Just some simple ways to talk about price.
To negotiate a little bit negotiate means we maybe don't like the price something is a little too much.
How can we push a little bit to get a lower price.
So we'll talk about a lot of things in this lesson and right now we'll start with vocabulary and phrases.