In the last lesson we talked about how you can start conversations in situations where you maybe don't
know other people but you have something in common.
And it's just a casual conversation perhaps free talk in this lesson.
It's related in this lesson we're going to talk about how you can have discussions.
But what's the difference.
Well starting a conversation is how to get it going.
What's the first thing you say.
Right.
But how to have discussions is for many more situations when you're with friends.
When you're with someone who you really want to talk to and maybe you'll sit down with a cup of coffee
and talk to them for a while for an hour.
How do you have a good conversation.
There are good discussions and bad discussions and I'm sure that you know what a good discussion feels
like and what a bad discussion feels like a good discussion means there's back and forth right.
It's not only one person talking.
Both people are talking.
Both people are listening.
Both people are giving opinions.
Ideally both people are asking questions.
So in this lesson we're going to talk about how you can keep a discussion going and how you can find
the interesting points around a topic related to a topic within a topic how you can find those things
and use them to explore deeply a topic.
To do this we need to be able to think abstractly.
That means we need to be able to think about a topic in a very general sort of way so that we can then
pick out those interesting things that can then be used to make questions that can then make the other
person think wow that's a good question.
I have a lot to say.
So let's actually get started with how we can do this in English.