In the last lesson we talked about expressions we can use for tough situations like negotiations tough
decisions and compromises.
In this lesson we're going to focus on technical language that means we're going to talk about how we
can order things for example days in the month.
We're going to talk about math problems.
Now it's not anything very very complicated but we need to be able to say that sort of technical language
that sort of technical English.
We're going to talk about dates we're going to talk a little bit about addresses symbols things like
that that you need to be able to say naturally without thinking.
In order to express basic things so that people can understand.
For example when you need to do something exactly where you need to go exactly how much of something
you have or you need.
This is a basic stuff but it's necessary to know it.
And it can be a little bit complicated.
So let's get started.
We're going to start with order.
We're going to start with the really easy stuff and then we'll slowly get a little bit more complicated.
Let's begin.