And the last lesson we talked about how to give advice to a friend which is a very important part of
a relationship because friends help each other in this lesson we're going to talk about the future how
we can talk about the future how we can explain what we're going to do in the future or what we may
do in the future.
Because some things are very certain.
Some things are not very certain.
So we're going to talk about different phrases that we can use to describe how sure or how certain we
are about things that are going to happen in the future.
And then we're going to talk about the causes of our actions and the results how we explain cause and
result and we'll look at some useful ways to express cause and result as well as what that means.
If you don't know then we'll talk about hypotheticals and I think you know what that means because we've
talked about it before but then we need to do that because we have to talk about possibilities things
that may happen in the future because we use very very similar grammar sometimes exactly the same grammar
to explain that.
Then finally we're going to actually do a real example in a job interview because in a job interview
you need to talk about your future.
So let's get started.