In the last lesson we talked about some exercises you can do to improve your spoken English and also
improve your habits when you're speaking English.
In this lesson we're going to do more of the same.
We're going to look at a couple of exercises and I should mention that a couple of these have been covered
in my other course called building your English brain.
So if you want to see more things like this then make sure to sign up for that course as well.
But these are just things that you can do to improve habits and it's less about actually learning words
and phrases and learning about how to handle situations which is what most of this course is about.
So let's actually go through what we're going to talk about in this lesson we're going to talk about
some basic vocabulary.
I'm going to teach you a few words then we're going to do some exercises about rephrasing.
Now we've done something similar in the last lesson.
It's a bit different.
And then we're going to do an exercise called the forward exercise.
We're going to practice that I'm going to show you how you can do it anytime you like.
And then we're also going to do something called improvisation which I will explain when we get to that
part.
So let's get started.