In the last lesson we talked about emails writing emails and how we can write different types of emails
for different purposes.
In this lesson we're going to talk about daily tasks things we need to do on a daily basis.
For example running errands or doing chores and we'll talk about both of those later on in the lesson.
So in this class we're going to cover some keywords first.
Then I'm going to talk about some tips to keep in mind when you're describing tasks that you need to
do on a daily basis on a daily basis and then we'll go into errands and I'll explain what that means
exactly and we'll give an example we'll do a couple of examples of running errands which is also a very
very important part of many of our lives.
Probably everyone watching this has done errands.
At some point unless you're a king or something queen but an errand is something that all of us do and
we need to know how to describe the errands that we run.
And if you don't know what that means now that's OK.
You will soon.
Let's begin.