In the last lesson we talked about cooking and cuisine.
How to talk about different types of food and how to describe a recipe how we prepare a particular dish.
In this lesson we're going to talk about a situation picking someone up at the airport.
Now this is a relatively common situation but we'll find as we go through this lesson.
A lot of common things that happen in regular conversations with people we meet usually for the first
time that we can also use in lots of other ways.
Lots of other situations.
I've written a dialogue similar to what I did for the hotel class.
So what we're going to do in this lesson is go through it step by step and explore the phrases that
we use at different points in the conversation and then we'll also expand that and talk about how we
can use those phrases for example in other similar situations.
So actually we're learning things that can be used in a wide variety of cases not only picking someone
up at the airport.
So let's begin.