In the last lesson we talked about how to tell a story and we talked about progress.
Connecting details in time in the past with our emotions and also what we were doing at that time in
a linear way linear.
By the way means in order this and this and then this and then this linear linear linear means in order.
OK well we're going to do something that's also in order in this lesson we're going to be talking about
how we order food in order.
That means you do this and then you do this.
It's linear.
OK.
We're going to talk about when you go to a restaurant how you ask for what you want how you explain
what you want.
And we're also going to talk about some of the other kinds of things you may need to say in the restaurant.
Some of the other things that may happen in the restaurant when you want to get your food.
That's what we're going to do in this lesson.
Now we're going to talk first about a couple of phrases that are important that you need to know when
you're going to ask for things and then we're going to actually look at how to talk with a waiter.
Some things you may need to say before you actually order your food.
Then we'll look at an example of an order how you would say what you want.
We'll look at a similar to real life example and then we'll talk about payment.
We'll talk a bit about how to ask for the check which is very simple and then we'll have a practice
as well.
So let's get started.