Sometimes you can't finish everything.
And it was a great meal and you still have what are called leftovers.
Leftovers from your meal you want to take them home put them in the refrigerator so you ask the waiter
or waitress as you're leaving.
Hey could excuse me could we get a to go box for this.
They'll bring you a box a to go box or a box to take this away.
Could we get a box to take this away.
Could you wrap this up to go to go and then they will take your food back to the kitchen.
Sometimes they'll do that for you.
Could you wrap this up to go.
So if you need a box.
Could we have to go box for this.
Or could we have a box box to take this away.
Very common.
Just in case you need to do that.
So I wanted to mention those because there are many times when the first cut you don't want to waste
it.
You can't leave it here.
Take it home eat it for lunch tomorrow.
That is a good idea.
So we've gone through the whole restaurant situation common phrases for asking for things how to interact
with the waiter or waitress how to interact with the hostess or host how to sit down and ask for a menu
how to order how to pay how to do all that stuff but to really get it.
You need to do it to find an online menu and record yourself ordering different combinations of things
from the menu.
Practice it.
Do it a few times and then if you can really do it go to a restaurant that's an English speaking restaurant
as soon as you can whether you're traveling you're on a trip be the one to order.
You've got to really practice it.
So first record yourself doing it get comfortable with it then the next time you're in an English speaking
restaurant.
Try these things out.
See how easy it is.
All right.
Good luck.