In the last lesson we went over some of the basics quanta fires to make sure that when we're speaking
either casually or in a more formal situation we don't make those basic mistakes.
Now we're going to go on in this lesson to something a bit more difficult something that a lot of people
even native English speakers are really afraid of making a presentation giving a presentation talking
in front of others about something.
Basically that's what a presentation is.
This is not just about the basics of doing a presentation.
We're actually going to build one together.
I'm going to show you how to build a presentation build an outline and then how to give it.
We're also going to talk about some dos and don'ts.
Basically things you should avoid and things you should make sure to remember when you're giving a presentation
and we're going to focus on hooks.
How to make your audience get interested in you and your topic.
Right from the very beginning we're also going to talk about how to interact with the audience when
you need to the end of the lesson.
I'm going to give a presentation based on the outline that we build in this lesson.
So we have a lot to do.
Let's begin.