In the last lesson we talked about how to order food obviously very very important.
And in this lesson we're going to talk about something maybe a little more fun but also something that
comes up very very often in daily conversations.
We're going to talk about how to talk about movies and TV shows.
First we're going to just go through some basic genres of movies.
Yes genres of movies.
I'll explain what that means.
If you don't know and then we're going to talk about some useful phrases we can use when we're describing
movies and TV shows or TV series then we're going to go over what exactly a review is.
In fact when we talk about movies and TV shows we are giving reviews when we recommend movies and TV
shows to friends.
We are kind of giving a review of that movie making a comment about it good or bad and then we're going
to actually look at some examples.
How can we describe a movie.
Basically this is called a synopsis and then how can we connect a review to that.
All right.
So let's get started and talk first about some basic movie generals.