In the last lesson we focused on common situations and expressions we can use in those situations.
In this lesson we're going to talk about how to book a hotel room and we're going to do it as a phone
call.
Now I realize that most of the time when you need to book a hotel room you can do it online.
I understand that but I believe that it's important to know how to do it.
If you need to and through the exercise of learning how to do it will also come across a lot of the
useful vocabulary related to hotels and customer service that you can use in lots of other situations
lots of other cases as well.
OK.
So hopefully by getting the feeling for this you'll have a better feeling for dealing with customer
service people and also have a deeper understanding of hotel related words and phrases.
So we're actually going to go through this as a dialogue.
I basically written a dialogue and we're going to go through it line by line and we'll also talk about
some of the alternative phrases that can be used instead of the lines that we're we're going through.
So let's get started with our hotel booking situation.