In the last lesson we focused on how to book a hotel room on the phone.
In this lesson we're going to talk about meetings how to handle meetings in English.
Now we're going to focus first on why we have meetings the function the purpose of meetings.
Then we're gonna go into proposals how to make a proposal and then for the other people listening to
a proposal.
How to give feedback and give comments.
Then we're going to actually go into for the person running a meeting.
Different things you can say to keep the meeting focused because that's one of the things you need to
do as a moderator.
The moderator is usually the person who's responsible for the meeting.
So meetings are of course for many different things and meetings could be with one person meetings could
be with a group of people.
I should be very clear at the beginning we're not going to cover every aspect of meetings.
We could probably do a full course just on meetings and the relationships between people in the office
right.
We could maybe do another course on that in the future.
But in this class we're going to really try to cover the most important elements of the typical meeting
with a group of people.
We won't really focus on the one to one type of meeting because that's really just a conversation.
But you should be prepared for this because we did our presentations class before and a proposal is
just a type of presentation so let's get started.
And just quickly go over some of the reasons that we need to have meetings.