In the last lesson we talked about technical language.
We talked about dates.
We talked about numbers.
We talked about math problems addresses in this lesson we're going to focus on common situations that
we need to deal with in daily life and expressions we can use to handle those situations.
So I want to be clear from the start the expressions that we use can be used often in many different
situations but we're going to learn them in the context of everyday situations that you will probably
come across on a regular basis.
OK so let's get started.
I'm going to introduce the situations and then I'm going to introduce the expressions that can be used
in those situations.
And then we'll talk about maybe some other ways that those expressions can be used.
So let's begin.