In the last lesson we talked about movies and TV very important in this lesson we're going to talk about
how to give advice.
Now this is different than what we would usually call recommending because sometimes recommending is
more about what should I order or what movie should I watch.
Advice is often more serious advice is usually about a problem that we're having in our lives or our
friends are having in their lives.
And so when we need help with this kind of thing we ask for advice in this lesson we're going to talk
about how we can ask for advice.
We're also going to talk about ways we can give advice some different phrases we can use for giving
advice then we're going to look at a specific example we're going to talk about some words and phrases
we can use to talk about fitness being overweight because that's the example that we're going to actually
look at how someone would give a friend advice using the words and phrases that we've learned to let's
get started.