In the last lesson we talked about everyday tasks things we need to do on a regular basis and how we
can describe those things clearly.
In this lesson we're going to talk about quanta fires basically a quanta Fire is an expression and you
know many of them which can give us a feeling for how many or how much of something we have without
using the specific number.
So we don't say one two three but basically do we have a large amount of something a small amount of
something.
What.
So we are looking at quantity and if I say a few oranges a few oranges you probably have a picture in
your mind for what that means.
Maybe you're picturing three or maybe four oranges on a table.
So that's a really good way to be able to communicate that the size or the amount of something clearly
or fairly clearly.
But there's a lot of confusion around quanta fires.
I know that you probably know most of them but we've got to make sure we use them correctly so that
we don't give the wrong impression so that we don't miss communicate.
So in this lesson we're going to first make sure we're very clear on countable vs. uncountable nouns.
We need to be very clear about that and then we'll get into some actual quanta fires and we'll go through
a lot of examples so that and I'm sure you know most of them already.
So that you're clear on exactly when they should be used and when they should not be used.
Let's get started.