In the last lesson we talked about how to give presentations and I hope that you've actually tried to
give your own presentation to practice all the things that we learned in this lesson we're going to
talk about difficulty how we can handle or deal with difficulty or disagreements if we don't disagree
with someone how do we describe that we're having a hard time how do we describe that so we're going
to learn quite a few new phrases in this lesson we're also going to go through a couple of specific
situations so we'll look at an example of bargaining and how two people can talk back and forth to find
a compromise.
I also want to talk about what a compromise is or when to learn a few phrases that we can use in compromise
situations or when we want to compromise.
Finally we're going to practice a few ways that we can give suggestions different than giving advice.
We want to weigh in on someone's difficult choice.
We have a difficult choice.
We'll talk about how we can describe that difficult choice and then how other people can say well it's
better if you do this it's better if you do that.
We call that weighing in sometimes.
All right let's get started.