In the last lesson we talked about words and phrases related to time how we can use those words and
phrases to express say different things in time.
In this lesson we're going to talk about writing good emails.
If you can write emails well even simple emails well then you make a good impression on others and that's
very very important and actually learning how to write good emails is not as hard as you may think.
We're gonna go over some basic tips and tricks that you can use things to remember when you're writing
emails and then we're going to look at two specific examples.
We're going to talk about how to write more casual emails to maybe friends or family members and then
we're also going to talk about how to write more professional emails especially to people that we know
who we may work with on a regular basis.
So let's get started with some tips for writing good emails.