In the last lesson we talked about meetings we talked about how to give feedback on a proposal and also
how to keep the meeting on track.
In this lesson we're going to be talking about food not everything about food.
We're going to focus mostly on cooking.
If you don't know how to describe cooking then in this lesson you are going to learn how to talk about
cooking food.
How to describe cooking and it's actually not as hard as you might think.
There are some simple things that we will learn which will be very useful when you want to describe
how to make something.
But at the beginning of the lesson we're going to talk about cuisine what exactly that means because
that's often a word that's misused and and misunderstood then we're going to talk about actions related
to cooking.
Then we're gonna focus on some of vocabulary and phrases useful vocabulary and phrases that we need
to know.
Then we'll get into a recipe will actually go through step by step a recipe for a particular dish.
We're actually going to do a Chinese dish.
I'm not a cooking expert but it will help us to practice the basics of describing how to cook.
So let's get started and talk about cuisine.